<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerViewDemo</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">
        Three Rings for the Elven-kings under the sky,
        \nSeven for the Dwarf-lords in their halls of stone,
        \nNine for Mortal Men doomed to die,
        \nOne for the Dark Lord on his dark throne
        \nIn the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie.
        \nOne Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them,
        \nOne Ring to bring them all, and in the darkness bind them
        \nIn the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie.</string>

    <string name="affirmation2">
        All that is gold does not glitter,
        \nNot all those who wander are lost;
        \nThe old that is strong does not wither,
        \nDeep roots are not reached by the frost.
        \nFrom the ashes a fire shall be woken,
        \nA light from the shadows shall spring;
        \nRenewed shall be blade that was broken,
        \nThe crownless again shall be king.
    </string>

    <string name="affirmation3">
        Learn now the lore of Living Creatures!
        \nFirst name the four, the free peoples:
        \nEldest of all, the elf-children;
        \nDwarf the delver, dark are his houses;
        \nEnt the earthborn, old as mountains;
        \nMan the mortal, master of horses:
        \n
        \nBeaver the builder, buck the leaper,
        \nBear bee-hunter, boar the fighter;
        \nHound is hungry, hare is fearful...
        \n
        \nEagle in eyrie, ox in pasture,
        \nHart horn-crownéd; hawk is swiftest,
        \nSwan the whitest, serpent coldest...
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation4">
        Far over the misty mountains cold
        \nTo dungeons deep and caverns old
        \nWe must away ere break of day
        \nTo seek the pale enchanted gold.
\n
        \nThe dwarves of yore made mighty spells,
        \nWhile hammers fell like ringing bells
        \nIn places deep, where dark things sleep,
        \nIn hollow halls beneath the fells.

        \nFor ancient king and elvish lord
        \nThere many a gleaming golden hoard
        \nThey shaped and wrought, and light they caught
        \nTo hide in gems on hilt of sword.
\n
        \nOn silver necklaces they strung
        \nThe flowering stars, on crowns they hung
        \nThe dragon-fire, in twisted wire
        \nThey meshed the light of moon and sun.
        \n
        \nFar over the misty mountains cold
        \nTo dungeons deep and caverns old
        \nWe must away, ere break of day,
        \nTo claim our long-forgotten gold.
\n
        \nGoblets they carved there for themselves
        \nAnd harps of gold; where no man delves
        \nThere lay they long, and many a song
        \nWas sung unheard by men or elves.
\n
        \nThe pines were roaring on the height,
        \nThe winds were moaning in the night.
        \nThe fire was red, it flaming spread;
        \nThe trees like torches blazed with light.
\n
        \nThe bells were ringing in the dale
        \nAnd men looked up with faces pale;
        \nThen dragon’s ire more fierce than fire
        \nLaid low their towers and houses frail.
\n
        \nThe mountain smoked beneath the moon;
        \nThe dwarves, they heard the tramp of doom.
        \nThey fled their hall, to dying fall
        \nBeneath his feet, beneath the moon.
\n
        \nFar over the misty mountains grim
        \nTo dungeons deep and caverns dim
        \nWe must away, ere break of day,
        \nTo win our harps and gold from him!
    </string>
    <string name="affirmation5">I have so much to be grateful for.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Good things are always coming into my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">New opportunities await me at every turn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">I have the courage to follow my heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things will unfold at precisely the right time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">I will be present in all the moments that this day brings.</string>
</resources>